50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
Ohh!
Ugh!
I'm so sorry.
It's not --
No, I know, not from the thing
that we did, but --
But it's the creature's...
...the residue that is...
Mm-hmm.
There's still some left.
Oh, right.
Oh, yes.
Oh!
Wait.
I still have your robe.
Gi!
Y-You should
still wear that.
Uh, it's very drafty
in here.
I'm gonna find
some clothes.
Very well. I'll, uh,
meet you outside, then?
Yes.
Well, I better go, 'cause,
you know, it's very drafty,
and you're not wearing
any clothes, either.
Yes.
I'll see you
in a bit, then.
Bye.
Where am I gonna
find some clothes?
Hmm.
Well...this could work.
Be careful.
I know.
This...has never
happened before.
What are you
going to do?
I don't know.
Ashi.
Hi.
This all looks
quite lovely.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
S-Should we sit?
Yes.
Oh, and I have food.
So do I.
A little chewy.
Yes.
Oh,
but still very good.
More?
No, thank you.
Jack, do you ever
think about home?
Every day.
My family, my home --
all of it.
My father was the emperor,
so we lived in the palace
overlooking the whole village.
It was so high up in the air
that it touched the clouds.
I would just stare out
at the beauty
of the seasons changing.
The summer sun
blanketed the valley
with long,
beautiful shadows.
The fall leaves
brought a bounty of color.
Winter was so white.
And the cherry blossoms
in the spring.
And...was there a girl?
Yes, many.
Oh!
Wait.
I -- You meagirl?
No, no.
I was only 8 when Aku came
and then everything...
Jack, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to...
It is nice to remember
the time before Aku.
It is the only way
I will ever see it again --
as a memory.
Jack?
Jack?!
Jack.
Aha!
Yeah, baby!
I really made it!
Whoo!
Wait.
What's that up ahead?
Aku?
What a welcome!
Aku, baby, I'm back.
Scaramouche has returned!
What the --
Hello.
You are now hearing
the voice of Aku!
Unfortunately,
I will no longer be available
for any more appointments.
I'm sorry for any inconvenience
this may have caused you.
Now, go!
Oh, no, baby.
I did not come all this way
for nothing.
Luckily,
Scaramouche knows scarymuch
about all the ins and outs,
babe.
Aku!
Go away.
Didn't you hear
the recording?
Leave me alone!
Oh, but, Aku-kachu,
I got some info on Jack-o
that's outta this world,
babe!
Ugh.
Whaaaat?!
Feast your ears on this.
I mean,
do you even have ears?
Like, can those antler things
even hear?
Get on with it!
Dig this, boss --
Jack-o has lost his sword-o.
Are you sure?!
Yes!
I'll bet my life on it!
What joy!
Yeah!
I'm back, baby!
Oh, yeah!
* Unh, unh,
doo-doo-doo doo-doo *
Oh, yeah!
* Doo-doo-doo-doo
doo-doo-doo *
Oh, yeah!
* Doo-doo-doo-doo
I know this place.
Jack...why?
Why did you just leave
like that?
You shouldn't
have followed me.
You need to go back.
Go back?
No.
I'm not going anywhere.
What's going on?
You don't understand.
So help me understand.
Jack.
All these years,
I have seen so many innocents
fall victim to Aku --
kind and decent people --
my friends, my family --
every one of them.
His evil has taken everything
I've ever...loved.
All I have left
are memories.
I do not want you
to become just a memory.
Jack, don't you see?
Everything that has
happened in our lives
has brought us here --
right now, together.
And together,
we're going to defeat Aku.
Samurai Jack!
Aku!
Aku?
It has been too long --
far, far too long.
But you're probably saying
to yourself,
"Why?
Why now for our sudden reunion?"
Well,
a little birdie told me...
...that Samurai Jack
has lost
the one thing
in the entire universe
that can destroy Aku!
You fooooooooooool!
Ugh?!
Oh, but, master I --
Well, it has been nice
catching up,
but I should go.
I don't want to interrupt
you and your lady friend.
Pretend I was never here.
I'll let myself out.
Aku!
Wait a minute.
I smell something --
something very familiar.
I smel me!
Madness!
Hold it!
Time out!
Really!
There's more Aku here,
besides me.
Stay back!
Yes.
I smell me inside of her.
Ashi.
Jack.
But how can that be?
I never -- Oh, wait.
There was that one time.
Aaaaaaaaakkkkkkkuuuuuuu.
Not bad.
Yes,
an attractive replica,
but it pales to the original.
Here!
Worship me,
daughters of Aku!
So she must have...
drank it?
And then...
Here you are,
a true daughter of Aku.
No!
Aku!
Oh?!
Yaaaagh!
Aaah!
Ashi?
I-I didn't do this!
Yes, you did.
Jack!
Ashi?
It's not me!
Of course it is,
sweetheart.
You wouldn't let
your daddy get hurt
by that bad ol' Samurai.
Jaaack!
I can't stop this!
I can't control myself!
You must fight it!
Fight!
Aah!
I'm trying!
Ashi, focus!
Break free!
I mean,
you try and raise them right,
then they run off
with your mortal enemy.
What's a dad to do?
Jack!
Nothing is working!
Don't give in.
Fight, Ashi.
Fight it!
Ashi,
you are not your father.
You are not your mother.
You are your own person.
You are good.
You can defeat him
from inside.
Boring!
Sweetheart, you have
to bring out your
best to defeat him,
and your best part
is meeeee!
Ashi!
Noooooo!
Ashi.
That's my girl.
Ashi?
Ashi!
Jack!
Kill me, Jack!
Kill me,
then destroy Aku!
Ashi!
You have to do it.
Do it now!
Kill me!
I can't.
Stooooooooooop!
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Back to the past,
Samurai Jack *
* Got to get back,
back to the past *
* Samurai Jack
* Watch out
* Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack *
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack